THIS PROGRAM CONTAINS AI-GENERATED CONTENT
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[sighs]
THE LABYRINTH PRISON MURDER CASE
[♪ theme music playing]
MURDER CLUB: LIAR'S TABLE
Hello.
FIRST PLAYER ENTERS
I'll just sit here.
AWKWARD
BEOMGYU
SINGER
- Hello.
- Wow.
- That must be the hot guy seat.
- This seat?
- Yeah.
I'd better sit here today.
Let's work as a team.
Are you into board games?
I've hardly played any.
But I really like playing the Mafia game.
If you're picked to be the mafia--
I become a lunatic.
CRAZY EYES
Even if I'm not the mafia,
I kill first and ask questions later.
HE'S DANGEROUS
I see.
- Yangrak!
- Hello.
[Yangrak] Hello. Gosh, you're both early.
- Hi.
Hello again.
Why are you sitting there?
I got bad vibes over there last time,
- so I switched to the other side.
- I see.
You rascal, Bokgil!
Oh, that's over. Sorry.
- Father.
- I thought he was still Bokgil.
[Yangrak] Good to see you.
PANI BOTTLE
YOUTUBER
[Jiyoon]
He says he's really good at Mafia.
How can someone be this handsome?
- [Jiyoon] Right?
- Thank you.
But his eyes
are kind of hard to read.
You should take out your contacts.
I can't. They're today's main feature.
[Pani Bottle] Doe eyes.
Yeah, I can't go without these.
If he ends up as the culprit…
- [Faker] Hello.
- [Beomgyu] Hello.
- Hello.
- Gosh.
- [Jiyoon] How…
I can't believe he's here.
- [Jiyoon] How did they get him here?
- Wow, we've got a real celebrity.
IN AWE
- [Pani Bottle] So, you know who he is?
- [Yangrak] Of course.
[Jiyoon]
He's the most famous person in the world.
- In the world?
- [Jiyoon] Yes.
No joke. He shuts down airports.
Even foreigners love him.
Nothing compared to Beomgyu.
Oh, please.
- [Jiyoon] You both shut down airports.
- You're a legend.
If they ended up at the same airport,
there would be an earthquake.
You're the most frequent flyer here.
Nobody stops me.
We once met at an airport.
- [Jiyoon] Really?
- At an airport?
- Yes.
I'm just amazed
because I've never seen
Faker on a show like this before.
- Never.
- [Jiyoon] Not once.
- So this is really unusual.
- Yeah, it is.
Well, I really love playing board games.
Do you go to board game cafes?
Yes, I do go once in a while.
And I have many board games at home.
FEELS LIKE A FAN MEET
I'm really excited to see
how you do today.
Totally. I can't wait.
And Beomgyu too,
since you like playing Mafia.
We'll surely catch the culprit today.
Absolutely.
Don't count on me too much.
I'm not good at deducing clues.
- Oh, come on.
- [Faker] I like to play but I'm not good.
Don't make excuses
when we're about to start.
They might turn the tables
and give him the key role.
- True.
- [Pani Bottle] He could be the culprit.
- For the views.
- [Jiyoon] Exactly.
That wouldn't be good.
He's got a great poker face.
I really don't think
I'll be able to read you at all.
IS THAT HIS POKER FACE RIGHT NOW?
Me? I'm just not very expressive.
[Jiyoon] Right?
I don't know if I'll be any good.
[host]
Welcome to Murder Club: Liar's Table.
SO IT BEGINS
Murder Mystery is
a competitive deduction game
where you try to identify
the culprit hidden among you.
You will each be assigned a unique role
and play the game as that character.
There is only one culprit,
but every player has their own secret.
To win this game,
you are allowed to lie, conceal the truth,
and act deceptively.
The game consists of five rounds.
At the start of each round,
one clue will be revealed
to the entire group,
and all the players will pick out
one card clue and one object clue.
The card clues are confidential
and can only be shared
during private conversations.
The object clues
can be examined by all players.
After collecting the clues,
you will have a 15-minute discussion.
Starting Round 2, you will have time
for private conversations.
After the group discussion,
you will have five minutes
to talk secretly
in the private conversation zones.
In Round 5, the final round,
you will make your final vote.
After the final group discussion,
you will vote for the person
you suspect to be the culprit.
Now, you will be assigned your roles.
Please choose one of the files
in front of you.
I want to do this one.
- [Jiyoon] Mr. P.
- Yeah.
I'm a traveler, so I'll go for Mr. T.
My surname is Lee, so I'll be Mr. L.
- L for LOL?
- Yes, L for League of Legends.
- I'll go for Mr. X.
- X? Okay.
- Thank you.
- [Yangrak] X?
- [Yangrak] X for X-Men.
- I pick H for Haaland!
H for Haaland?
CHARACTER SELECTION COMPLETE
All right.
THE CULPRIT HAS BEEN CHOSEN
[host]
Today's game is set in a labyrinth prison.
To make it impossible
for inmates to escape,
the labyrinth prison has
an extremely complex high-security system.
It is also automatically managed
around the clock
by a state-of-the-art AI system.
So we're currently prisoners, right?
I think we're on the same team.
We're fellow inmates.
We were all part of the same
phone scam operation.
- Yeah.
- We worked as a team.
But we never saw each other's faces.
Today's our first time seeing each other.
We only go by our aliases.
- We only interacted by voice.
- Only aliases.
We can reveal our roles, right?
We can discuss what we all know,
but the rest is confidential.
So what was your role on the outside?
I acted as a kind of influencer.
I was on the stock-tip team.
I reeled in subscribers.
32, INFLUENCER,
INVESTMENT ADVISER AND VIP ACCOUNT MANAGER
What about you, Mr. X?
I did all sorts of odd jobs.
I just did whatever I was told.
You're the baby of the group.
I wasn't tied to one team
but helped out here and there.
I was also a cash courier.
25, CASH COURIER,
THE ORGANIZATION'S GOFER
YOU LAUGH?
It's just--
I worked really hard!
- Don't laugh.
- [Jiyoon] Okay.
- You're an essential member.
- Of course.
You couldn't do without me.
You've probably heard this before.
"Hello, this is
the District Prosecutors' Office."
"Your bank account has been compromised."
- It was my idea.
- [Faker] It all starts with his idea.
45, PHONE SCAM TEAM LEADER,
CALL CENTER SCRIPT WRITER
- [Yangrak] It's a key role.
- As for me,
I'm the… [in English] …engine…
[in Korean] …of this operation.
- [in English] Engine?
- [Jiyoon] Engine?
[in Korean] To run a phone scam,
- you need servers and things like that.
- [gasps]
I'm in charge of building
and managing that technology.
[Pani Bottle]
The coding and hacking expert.
[Jiyoon]
You're the heart of the operation.
36, GENIUS HACKER,
SERVER OPERATOR
My role is the most important.
You work to get paid, after all.
- Right?
- [Jiyoon] Yeah.
I'm a former tax investigator
who designed the money-laundering scheme.
[Yangrak] You're the financial expert.
39, FORMER TAX INVESTIGATOR,
MONEY LAUNDERING AND FINANCES MANAGER
- That's the most crucial role…
- [Beomgyu] Yeah.
…since we're in it for the money.
That's right.
What are your charges?
- [Yangrak] Mine is--
- I'll go first.
I violated the Capital Markets Act.
- Market manipulation, Ms. H?
- I believe so.
I was sentenced to two years.
- That's lenient.
- [Jiyoon] Not too bad.
- [Pani Bottle] That's short.
- [Beomgyu] You'll be out soon.
- Mr. X…
- [Faker] Yes?
…committed fraud.
Fraud?
- He tricked them with his doe eyes.
- [Yangrak] What a waste of good looks.
I was sentenced to three years for fraud.
- Three years?
- [Faker] Yes.
I was
sentenced to six years.
- They're getting longer.
- [gasps]
- You a bad man.
- Six years. What was the charge?
Participating in a criminal organization.
SENTENCED TO 6 YEARS
- Two, three and six years?
- [Yangrak] They're getting longer.
- Ten for you?
- I call 12!
12? Bingo.
- 12 years?
- [Jiyoon] It's 3, 6, 12.
I got 12 years for violating
the Electronic Financial Transactions Act.
- [Faker] Financial transactions?
- You dirtbag.
What did you call me?
Oh, you mean Mr. T.
- Yes, Mr. T's a dirtbag.
- Yeah, Mr. T.
He got 12 years.
- How about you, sir?
- I got--
- A life sentence?
- No.
Sorry to disappoint you.
I got half of what you got.
- [Jiyoon] Six years?
- Yeah.
- Why is mine the longest?
- [Yangrak] Listen.
I was convicted
of "aggravated financial crimes."
Basically, fraud.
Hey, samesies!
We're comrades. [in English] Let's get it!
[Jiyoon, in Korean]
You're both fraudsters.
For people like us, a long prison sentence
is proof of how hard we worked.
- [Jiyoon] That's right.
- It's a badge of honor.
[host] Today's murder took place
during an escape attempt.
Your criminal operation
is run by a ringleader.
Members of the organization
refer to him as MASTER.
The organization is a cell-based network
with him at the center,
but no one knows who the MASTER is.
After the members
were locked up in prison,
the main members
followed the MASTER'S orders
and secretly planned an escape.
On the day of the murder,
through a broker sent by the MASTER,
each member received
a revolver and six bullets.
At midnight, the prison doors opened
and the members were meant to meet
at the central control tower
to escape together.
The control tower was equipped
with a control system
and was also connected
to an escape route leading outside.
They could only escape
through the control tower.
But once the escape plan was underway,
multiple gunshots rang out
throughout the prison.
One shot at 00:15,
four shots at 00:21,
one shot at 00:25,
and two shots at 00:30.
CASE TIMELINE
There were four rounds
of a total of eight gunshots.
Realizing something had gone wrong,
all the members
headed for the control tower.
When they arrived, they discovered
a body hanging with both hands cuffed.
Was the MASTER
also trying to escape with us?
He planned the whole route
for us to escape
and also provided us with guns.
He's the top boss.
He was waiting at the control tower
so he could escape with us.
- To escape together?
- [Ms. H] Yeah.
Has anyone seen his face?
- [Mr. T] No.
- None of us have.
[Ms. H] I don't know what he looks like.
MASTER
PHONE SCAM, MONEY LAUNDERING, SERVER ADMIN
CASH COURIER,
INVESTMENT ADVISER & VIP MANAGER
[host] Here is your first shared clue.
[Ms. H] Gosh, how chilling.
[Mr. X] He's dead in this picture, right?
This is the victim,
who we think is the MASTER, right?
The dead person is the MASTER for sure.
- So he's the MASTER.
- [Mr. T] Yeah.
His hands are raised,
- and there are bullet marks…
- [Mr. P] Here and there.
[Mr. T] …one each on the left and right.
- [Mr. P] One on either side?
- [Mr. T] Yeah.
So someone shot
from this side and that side?
- Two shooters?
- One from the left. One from the right…
But the fact that he is
hanging from the window
means someone came in
and hung him up, right?
But why would they do that?
As punishment.
RIDICULOUS
They made him raise his hands
as punishment.
You don't seem to be a fan of our MASTER.
I'm sensing some hostility.
No. I have no idea who he is.
But if the MASTER is dead…
Once we get out,
we need a way to make money.
So why kill the MASTER?
- It had to be someone who hated him.
- [Mr. L] That's right.
So I was curious of our relations to him.
- He's our boss. Why would we hate him?
- [Ms. H] Right?
But our youngest said something fishy--
- I'm just the baby. I don't know anything.
- [Mr. P] Right.
KEEPING A WATCHFUL EYE
[host] Round 1 will now begin.
First, pick out the card clues.
Every player
has a total of five card clues.
Each card contains a secret
that no other player knows.
In every round except for the fifth round,
the players can take one card
from the person they suspect.
Use the collected clues
to determine who the culprit is.
I'll take a card from Mr. T.
[Mr. P] Gosh.
I'll take one from Mr. L.
Why do you all suspect me?
- You won't find anything.
- [Mr. T] Mr. P.
- Mr. X.
- Yes?
- If it's no bother, pass me a card.
- Which one?
- The middle one.
- The middle one?
- Thanks.
- [Ms. H, Mr. T laugh]
- I'll take one from Mr. X too.
- [Mr. X] Sure.
I'm popular.
THE PLAYERS CAN SHARE
WHAT THEY KNOW FROM THE CARD CLUES
BUT THEY CAN ONLY SHOW THE ACTUAL CARD
DURING PRIVATE CONVERSATIONS
[host] The evidence zone is open.
Please bring over one evidence each
and resume the group discussion.
EVIDENCE ZONE
EACH PLAYER MAY COLLECT
1 OBJECT CLUE PER ROUND
THE OWNER OF THE CLUE IS UNSPECIFIED
[Mr. T] There's a pile of evidence here.
OBJECT CLUES COLLECTED
- Can we examine them right away?
- [Mr. T] Yes.
- I guess we share these.
- [Mr. T] Yes, they're shared clues.
[Mr. X] This is mine.
- Delivery?
- [Mr. T] Part-time delivery?
When I was drifting,
unsure of what to do for a living,
I needed a way to get by,
so I responded to this flyer.
- So this is a clue about you?
- Yes.
- You brought a clue about yourself.
- [laughs] His own clue.
[Mr. X] Yeah, I guess so.
Oh, is this flyer how you joined our team?
- The delivery job was for us.
- I thought it was a plain job.
This is how he ended up
being a cash courier.
- Yes, that's right.
- [Ms. H] He responded to this flyer.
[sniffles] I needed the money.
Were you unemployed at the time?
- I was a K-pop trainee…
- [Ms. H] Okay.
…but I failed to debut
and felt like a burden to my parents.
I felt aimless
and I lost my faith in people.
So I took this job
just as a means to make money.
I'm aware of Mr. X's past.
The card clue I took from him
was a post on an online
fan community forum,
so I know he's not lying about his past.
MR. X IS A FORMER K-POP IDOL TRAINEE
I brought this.
A VIP…
ROUND 1 OBJECT CLUE
VIP CARD
- It belongs to Mr. T.
- Oh, it's mine.
What were you a VIP member of?
- Do you see the dice?
- [Mr. X, Mr. L] Yeah.
- [Mr. T] I think--
- A casino?
Yeah, card squeezing and stuff like that.
Do you like gambling?
I do enjoy it.
I don't think we found any key evidence.
Don't just brush this aside.
It could be a key clue.
It might be important,
so I'll hold on to it for now.
- No.
- I'm going to need it.
I'm gambling again after I escape.
HE'S A CONFIRMED ADDICT
Ms. H, what did you find?
Well, you are aware
that this prison is
structured around AI, right?
- [Mr. L] Yes.
- [Ms. H] It's run by an AI system.
There is an AI automated log.
- [Mr. L] This is important evidence.
- It's crucial.
[Mr. T]
Were the shots fired from the inside?
"Analysis of the interior wall
on the second floor shows
two bullet impact marks
on each corner of the wall."
"Timeline analysis."
"The shots were fired at the same time
or in close succession."
"It's highly likely there was
an exchange of gunfire."
One bullet mark in each corner,
likely fired at the same time.
- So they were shooting at each other?
- [Ms. H] I guess so.
WAS THERE A SHOOT-OUT
IN THE CONTROL TOWER?
I got evidence about Ms. H.
- It concerns me?
- [Mr. L] It's to do with you.
"I am deeply saddened to inform you
that Eom Jihoon passed away
in an accident early this morning."
It's a text message concerning
the death of Eom Jihoon.
Was he your brother?
He was my younger brother.
Your brother died?
We're currently preparing for his funeral.
MS. H'S BROTHER DIED?
I found a news article.
ROUND 1 OBJECT CLUE
NEWS CLIPPING
"Exclusive: Phone scam gang on the run
got into a car crash."
"Technical mastermind seriously injured."
"Members of a large phone scam ring
operating from overseas servers
caused a car crash
while fleeing from investigators,
and a key member of the group
is confirmed to be seriously injured."
"A passenger sustained
severe lower-body injuries
and was taken to the hospital."
"The passenger in question
oversaw the group's technical operations,
including its systems and servers."
Isn't this about Mr. L?
- [Ms. H] Yes, it is Mr. L.
- It's about me.
I was involved in an accident
where I injured my leg
while fleeing with my older brother.
So that's what this is referring to.
MR. L INJURED HIS LEG WHILE ON THE RUN
His leg was permanently impaired.
He had no trouble walking earlier.
- [Mr. P] Didn't you bring anything?
- Yes, I did.
PERFECTLY FINE
You caught me on a good day.
[laughing]
HIS LEG HAS GOOD DAYS AND BAD DAYS
It seems to be flaring up again.
[Ms. H] Is it? Your right leg? Okay.
You were fleeing with your brother.
What was his role?
My brother is actually the MASTER.
- What?
- [Mr. P] Are you serious?
- Wait. Your brother's the MASTER?
- [Mr. T] He's your brother?
Your brother is the MASTER?
But this could be a lie, right?
It could be…
MASTER'S YOUNGER BROTHER?
I'm telling you this
so we can quickly identify his killer.
Find out who betrayed him and escape.
Or maybe you killed your brother
to take over as the MASTER.
But I have no reason to do that.
[Mr. X] Are you rich?
SUSPICIOUS
By the way,
in this picture of my dead brother,
you can see bloodstains on the window.
That means
the shots were fired from inside,
causing the blood to splatter like this.
- [Mr. X] Shot from the inside?
- What do you think?
I think that's right.
- Right?
- Yes.
DID THE SHOOTING HAPPEN INSIDE?
Oh, no lenses on these glasses.
ROUND 1 CARD CLUES
COUNSELING RECORDS, FAN FORUM POST
DISCIPLINARY REPORT,
AI PRISON GUARD'S TESTIMONY
[host]
Here is the shared clue for Round 2.
[Mr. T, Mr. P]
"Labyrinth prison survey report."
[Mr. P] Total height is 17 m.
- This is the crime scene, right?
- [Mr. T] Yeah.
The area below is a blind spot.
THIS AREA CANNOT BE SEEN
FROM THE CONTROL ROOM
[host] Please exchange card clues.
All right.
- I got one from Mr. T.
- I'll go for Ms. H.
I'll take a card from you.
I'll take one from Mr. X.
X for me too.
I'll take X's last remaining card.
- [Ms. H] Mr. X is out of cards.
- [Mr. X] Yeah.
MR. POPULAR
- [Mr. T] I feel clueless.
- [Mr. P] Oh, man.
These games are getting harder.
Look, he's limping!
His leg is hurting.
[Ms. H] It seems to come and go.
[Mr. X] His leg's suddenly flaring up.
Yeah, it's feeling worse.
The letter "I."
OBJECT CLUES COLLECTED
[Mr. P]
We'll never catch the killer at this rate.
[♪ whimsical music playing]
[Ms. H] What's this? Is it a clue?
- That's nothing.
- No, it's not.
- [Ms. H] Is it ours?
- That's the cam shooting us.
- [players laughing]
- Oh, I thought it was evidence.
- I was about to check the SD card.
- [Mr. P] No.
- Just this, then?
- [Mr. T] There's more.
It's just a production camera.
- [Mr. X] So funny.
- [Ms. H] I'm too immersed in the game.
My clue is a mobile phone.
- [Mr. P] A mobile phone?
- Yeah. I wonder whose it is.
Can you turn it on?
[Mr. L] Look in the photo gallery.
- [Mr. P] What?
- I just got chills.
- Why?
- [Mr. T] Whose is it? Who's that?
- [Mr. L] It's a family photo.
- Look.
- This is…
- Mr. P?
[Ms. H]
It seems to be a photo of Mr. P's family.
These two are his family.
I'm guessing this is
his wife and daughter.
But the ages don't seem to add up.
How old are you, Mr. P?
I'm 35 years old.
What are you saying? [chuckles]
[Mr. P] I'm 35!
I don't believe you
since you're a scammer.
His job took a toll on him.
What can he do?
If he's really 35,
then I think this is his wife.
MR. P IS A FAMILY MAN
WITH A WIFE AND DAUGHTER?
I found evidence dating back ten years
about the adoption of a female minor.
This is the admission record.
"She was placed
in a child protection facility."
Ten years ago.
I think it's her.
The adopted girl.
Do you think so?
I never adopted anyone.
If it was ten years ago,
she might be the adoptee.
CRACKING UP
What is the family connection here?
Are they his daughter and grandchild
or his wife and daughter?
Come on. Don't attack me about my looks.
She is my daughter.
I learned from the MASTER
and joined the organization
to strike it rich.
But I needed a caregiver.
I put her into care so that I could work.
HE ABANDONED HIS DAUGHTER
TO JOIN A CRIMINAL ORGANIZATION
Is there any other evidence?
- [Mr. P] What's that?
- "You're under arrest."
- [Mr. P] We're no strangers to handcuffs.
- [Mr. X] We basically
wear them like bracelets.
Are they the ones that were used
to hang the MASTER
when he died?
Oh, there's blood on it.
- [Mr. L] So there is.
- If you look here…
BLOODSTAINED HANDCUFFS
If he was dead, he should have collapsed,
but he's hanging by those handcuffs.
I find that really strange.
Don't you think killing someone
and then hanging them up
is a bit psycho?
Of course.
A normal person wouldn't do this.
Well, actually…
- I hung him up.
- What?
THE PSYCHO IS AMONG US
[Mr. T, Mr. P, Mr. X laughing]
TOTALLY UNFAZED
- [Mr. X] Why?
- Well--
THIS KIND OF BRAZEN CONFESSION IS A FIRST
- I hung my brother up.
- [Mr. P] Why?
Yes, I hung him up,
but he was still alive
when I handcuffed him.
We got into a fight
so I had no choice but to restrain him.
And then I left,
but when I came back, he was dead.
Around what time did that happen?
I think I handcuffed him
between 00:16 and 00:19.
-The first…
- [Mr. P] You should know, you hung him up.
I tied him up and left,
but when I came back, he was dead.
- In that time?
- [Mr. L] Yes, so…
Within a few minutes?
I really want to find
the person who killed him.
[chuckles]
Even though you got into a fight?
So far, you are the most likely suspect.
- Can you explain why you cuffed him?
- Yeah. We had a fight--
That's no reason to handcuff him
and hang him from the ceiling.
Were you mad he left you behind
when the car crashed?
That was part of the reason.
That's a strange reason.
Why did he leave after cuffing him?
They were alone, so he could have
easily cuffed him normally.
And he has a bad leg,
so that'd be less trouble.
It's common for accomplices to fight.
They could have fought over profits.
But I don't think Mr. L
would kill his brother over money.
I think it would be a family issue,
maybe some kind of betrayal.
At this point, it's hard to say.
- I brought evidence on myself.
- Mr. T.
- Yes.
- A diary?
- [Mr. P] Are you confessing?
- [Mr. T] It's nothing like that.
Business was good back then.
[Mr. T]
"1.78 billion won. 3.18 billion won."
We were rolling in money.
MR. T APPROVED AND MANAGED THE FUNDS
- Whose is it?
- [Mr. T] It's mine.
- You mean it's ours.
- [Mr. T] Right, that's what I meant.
SETTING HIM STRAIGHT
What evidence did you bring, Mr. P?
[Mr. P] I found this.
Hey, this is pretty major.
- You think so? I thought--
- Hang on.
- I'm a bit clueless.
- Because this log is just
the ledger of the money
we made from our scam.
- That's all it is. You need to see this.
- Okay.
This is what really matters.
- Bullet marks.
- Where is this?
Oh, they're mine!
[Mr. T] What?
I fired four bullets.
I was so startled,
I fired four shots into the wall.
EVERYTHING IS HIS
He's so excited to see evidence
about the shots he fired.
Didn't you hear four shots
at around 00:21?
I was startled by a sound,
so I shot in that direction.
But why did you shoot?
I was on the move at the time,
and I heard the sound
of someone chasing after me--
- You weren't in the control tower?
- No.
- I was at the far end.
- [Mr. L] Were you past the gate?
At the outer walls. I was really startled.
I only meant to shoot one bullet.
I didn't know it'd keep firing.
Did you have any bullets left over?
- Yes.
- [Mr. L] You had more bullets.
Someone look at this.
I can't figure it out.
"A equals 17. B equals 22."
What does this mean?
- A equals 10?
- [Mr. P] It's 17.
And B equals 22.
- What?
- I don't know.
I'm really bad at math.
[Ms. H] What was A?
A is 17 and B is 22.
[Ms. H] A is 17 and B is 22?
WHAT IS THIS MYSTERY EQUATION?
Honestly, I'm totally clueless so far.
It's hard to guess who it could be.
Didn't this just prove
that I never shot anyone?
It proves you shot four bullets then,
but shots were fired after that.
[Mr. X] Yeah, around three more.
And you had bullets left over
after those four shots.
But there was a shot fired before this.
I think that was me.
Initially…
WHAT IS HE SAYING?
- You fired shots?
- Yeah.
But earlier, you said you just cuffed him.
But we had a pretty big fight before that.
- You used a gun on your brother?
- You didn't just throw fists?
What kind of brothers shoot at each other?
Did he get hit?
He did.
- What?
- [Ms. H] Where did he get hit?
This doesn't make sense.
You get into a fight
and aim at your brother?
What kind of siblings fight with guns?
Ones from a dysfunctional family.
- [Mr. P] A total trainwreck.
- [Mr. X] Yeah.
What time did you shoot him?
I shot him at around 00:15.
[Mr. P] You're a scary guy.
FIRST GUNFIRE
[host] Starting Round 2,
the private conversation zones are open.
Anyone who wants a private conversation
can freely access this zone.
I reckon we all want to talk to Mr. L.
I'm up for it.
Then, why don't we three talk first?
Then, I'll talk to Bokgil. [chuckles]
I'm not Bokgil.
I'm Mr. P.
We need to quickly find the traitor.
You're the traitor,
but you're acting innocent.
I had no reason to kill my brother.
Even though you shot him?
That was because he shot me first.
- The first gunfire was a single shot.
- [Mr. X] Yeah.
[Mr. L] The first shot in the timeline
was the sound
of me and my brother fighting.
But then we should have heard two shots.
But we both fired at the same time.
So you would have just heard one shot.
Then the clue we saw earlier,
the AI-analysis report,
was about your fight with your brother.
Yeah, I shot my brother,
and it grazed his arm here.
- [Mr. X] It wasn't fatal?
- It wasn't life-threatening.
I also got shot in the shoulder,
so it hurts a little.
Your shoulder too?
My injury was worse than his.
If you ever want to play e-sports
after you get out…
[Mr. X] You're at a disadvantage.
Who are you? Where are you from?
- I am… [chuckles]
- [chuckles]
Ms. H.
- My name is H.
- Yeah.
- I used to be an influencer.
- Right.
I wanted to make big money.
Same as me.
[clicks tongue] I found out
through a friend
- about the MASTER.
- A friend?
SHE HEARD ABOUT THE MASTER
AT A SOCIAL GATHERING OF ELITES
- I need the MASTER.
- [Mr. P grunting]
I wanted to use him to get filthy rich.
Me too! We're the same.
[Ms. H] Yeah.
- I needed him to stay alive.
- [Mr. P] Same.
I was so shocked to find out he was dead.
My question for you is,
you had a gun, right?
Of course.
When did you use it?
- I didn't.
- You didn't use it?
- Not at all?
- Never.
If I find evidence that you're lying,
you're the culprit.
I never fired, I tell you.
- So you never used it.
- Right.
Gun? No way.
- [Ms. H] I--
- Did you use yours?
[Ms. H] Well, I…
Let's talk about you.
- [chuckling] I don't know--
- I'll do the note-taking.
- Hey, this is my confidential file.
- [Mr. P chuckling]
[Ms. H] Write your notes here. Gosh.
If we escaped with the MASTER,
we could get filthy rich, right?
So I was making my way
to the MASTER when I heard a shot.
So I fired a bullet by accident.
I pulled the trigger
because I was so scared.
- To be honest, I also fired a shot.
- What?
You liar!
But I didn't shoot at a person.
I shot a cabinet.
I kept another item stored in a cabinet.
- I used my gun…
- Yeah?
…to get that item
and pass it on to the MASTER.
- To open the cabinet?
- That's right.
I didn't know the passcode.
HE USED HIS GUN TO OPEN THE CABINET?
Why did you leave
after shooting your brother?
I went to the storage room
to find a hard disk.
Why did you need to find a hard disk?
THE HARD DISK CONTAINS KEY DATA
ABOUT THEIR ORGANIZATION
HE HID A BACKUP HARD DISK OF THE SERVER
IN THE STORAGE ROOM BEFORE IMPRISONMENT
There's a hard disk in the storage room,
and we can't let the police
get their hands on it.
Oh, you wanted to destroy the evidence?
HE WENT FROM THE CONTROL TOWER
TO THE STORAGE ROOM AT 00:19
Can you share your alibis,
from the beginning?
I need to know where you were
at 00:21, 00:25, and 00:30.
THE CHARACTER GUIDES SHOW
THE TIMELINE OF THEIR MOVEMENTS
For ten minutes,
I had no idea what to do,
so I just waited.
- I was just too anxious.
- Right.
Since it's such a complex labyrinth,
I thought circling the perimeter was best.
MR. X MOVED AROUND THE OUTSIDE
TO GET HIS BEARINGS
WORKSHOP 2, DINING HALL 2, SHOWERS
Staying by the perimeter,
I went from the showers to Workshop 1.
[Mr. T] The showers?
[Mr. X] I passed the showers
and Workshop 1.
And that's where I heard
a strange sound and fired.
- By Workshop 1?
- Yeah. It was 00:21 at the time.
HE HEARD SOMEONE COMING
AND FIRED FOUR BULLETS
After that,
I passed Gate 3
to get to the control tower.
What time was that?
- It was around 00:35.
- [grunts]
HE ARRIVED AT THE CONTROL TOWER
AT AROUND 00:35
- [Mr. X] Mr. T.
- I set out from the green zone,
and at around 00:10,
I found that Gate 1 was locked,
so I went through the showers to Gate 2.
I got to Gate 2 through the showers,
but it wouldn't open.
So I got a bit anxious at that point.
In the corridor between Gate 2
and the showers,
I stood around for a bit
not knowing what to do.
- My mind went blank.
- [Mr. L] You zoned out?
HE ZONED OUT?
What were you doing at 00:25?
Yeah. What did you at 00:25?
Oh, that's when I zoned out.
- Until 00:25?
- [Mr. L] What about at 00:30?
It doesn't say what I did at 00:25.
- At 00:30, at Gate 3--
- It doesn't say?
No, at 00:30,
I learned Gate 3 was open,
so I went there.
Got it.
Okay. You don't remember?
- It really doesn't say!
- You don't know your alibi.
Got it.
Mr. T's alibi is a bit suspicious.
He wouldn't tell us.
He's definitely hiding something.
ROUND 2 CARD CLUES
CRUMPLED NOTE, SEARCH HISTORY
FIREARM INSPECTION LOG,
H'S FRIEND'S TESTIMONY, CCTV AUDIO RECORD
[host] Here is the next shared clue.
[Mr. X] You can tell
from the number of bullets.
[Ms. H] We all fired at least once.
5 OUT OF 6 BULLETS REMAINING
2 OUT OF 6 BULLETS REMAINING
Holding the trigger down
doesn't release a bullet.
5 OUT OF 6 BULLETS REMAINING
[host] Please exchange card clues.
- Go ahead.
- [Ms. H] I'll take one from Mr. P.
Why me? You didn't suspect me earlier.
Hang on. I'll take this one.
MR. P TAKES ONE FROM MR. L
Mr. P has many cards left,
so I'll take one from him.
I'll take one from Ms. H.
I'm also starting to wonder about Ms. H.
I got something heavy.
What's this?
[Mr. L] The letter "O."
ROUND 3
Gosh. Mr. L, you are rich.
This looks like a ledger
showing the profit shares
of Mr. L and the MASTER.
- He did it for the money.
- [Mr. T gasps] He took his cut.
You killed your brother over money.
I also have a lot of evidence
related to finances.
- I have Eom Jihoon's account details.
- [all gasping]
- Your late brother.
- Yeah.
- [Mr. L] He was your brother, right?
- Yes.
[Mr. L] He wired the MASTER
three installments of 50 million won.
- Three installments.
- [Mr. T] Who did?
- My brother.
- [Mr. T] Your brother?
- Was he a victim of the scam?
- [Mr. X] He must have been.
He killed him over 50 million won?
- 150 million won.
- Oh, 150 million?
He was scammed three times,
so it was 150 million.
This means Ms. H
had a clear motive to kill the MASTER.
Eom Jihoon is actually my ex-husband.
I killed him. [chuckling]
They all just assumed he was my brother.
"Right! My brother!"
and I went along with it.
I found out through a friend
about the MASTER.
SHE THOUGHT HER HUSBAND WAS RICH
HE WAS THE FRONT MAN
OF THE MONEY-LAUNDERING COMPANY "PANTS"
THE MASTER WAS SOMEONE ELSE
SHE CHOSE TO DITCH HER HUSBAND
AND BEGAN TO OBSESS OVER
GAINING REAL POWER
WHAT WAS AMBITIOUS MS. H'S PLAN?
But I had no idea my brother
wired the MASTER money.
Are you sure about that?
How can we believe that?
Of course, I could be lying.
But one thing's for sure.
I stood to gain a lot from meeting
the MASTER on the outside,
so I could never kill him.
You weren't trying to get out
of the organization by killing him?
No, I wasn't.
I'm so shocked by this evidence.
But that doesn't add up
because didn't you read
an upsetting memo saying…
- Me?
-…you'd be sorted out after the escape?
She would be sorted out after escaping?
- Yeah, didn't you see that memo?
- I did.
Doesn't that mean
you were going to be killed?
No, it meant we'd wipe the slate clean
and start afresh together
so we could stand tall.
No, that's spinning it too positively.
DID THE MASTER PLAN TO KILL MS. H?
[host] Starting Round 3,
the CCTV zone is open.
Use the password cards
to access the security footage.
CCTV ZONE
CCTV PASSWORD ON BONUS CARD
FOUND NEXT TO OBJECT CLUE
I'll check out the CCTV.
- Can I go with you?
- [Mr. T] Of course.
RUSHING OVER
[Mr. X] I see you can still run
with that leg.
- The pain's eased up again.
- [Mr. X chuckles]
[exclaims]
- What's this?
- Who's that?
- [Mr. X] "I will shoot."
- [Mr. L] Gate 4.
"I will shoot you!"
- [Ms. H] Is that me?
- [Mr. L] Who is that?
SHE LOWERED HER GUN WITHOUT SHOOTING
[Mr. X] Two shots were fired at 00:31.
But she decided not to shoot.
- She didn't shoot?
- [exclaims]
- She didn't shoot.
- [Mr. X] It seems not.
MORE CCTV FOOTAGE
- What's that?
- [exclaims]
[gasps]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Oh, my.
I told you earlier, didn't I?
That's how you opened the cabinet?
I'm cleared! I'm in the clear.
HE SHOT THE CABINET TO OPEN IT
- What was inside it?
- What was in there?
WHAT DID HE PULL OUT OF THE CABINET?
My cover was almost blown,
but they haven't caught on.
I'm actually an undercover cop.
I shot the cabinet to get
the hidden investigation records.
But since it's such a big murder case,
that evidence has taken a back seat.
It's a relief.
MR. P IS AN UNDERCOVER COP
- I'll enter my password now.
- Sure.
Who's that?
- Who is that?
- Who's that?
- Who is it?
- Who is that?
- You said you went to the storage room.
- I did.
You went to get the hard disk.
I went to the storage room
to find a hard disk.
But I failed to find the disk.
- I think that's what you're seeing.
- [Ms. H] What?
MR. L TRIED TO RETURN
TO THE CONTROL TOWER AT 00:29
I have one more.
[♪ intriguing music playing]
- [Mr. P] You… Hang on.
- The hard disk.
MS. H TOOK SOMETHING OUT
OF THE STORAGE ROOM AT 00:10
It's the hard disk.
- She took it.
- Earlier…
I took that hard drive.
- Why?
- How'd you know about it?
We need that disk to work with the MASTER.
[Mr. P] To get filthy rich.
THE FINAL CCTV CLUE
- Who's that?
- Oh, I know.
- [Ms. H] He's limping.
- [Mr. P] Right.
MR. L ENTERED THE CONTROL TOWER
What's he doing?
-He suddenly stopped limping!
- What the heck?
- He suddenly stopped limping!
- [Mr. T] What the heck?
Whoa, that's chilling!
HE WAS LIMPING WHEN HE WENT IN
BUT HE WASN'T LIMPING 10 MINUTES LATER
Sometimes you're limping,
sometimes you're not.
What a crazy twist.
Oh!
You're the MASTER.
Translation by Hannah Og Nam